{
    {"problem": "카이", "answer": "스트", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "도라", "answer": "에몽", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "삼시", "answer": "세끼", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "스폰", "answer": "지밥", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "원두", "answer": "커피", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "아는", "answer": "형님", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "게르", "answer": "마늄", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "덤프", "answer": "트럭", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "와이", "answer": "파이", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "비트", "answer": "코인", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "알레", "answer": "르기", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "탄수", "answer": "화물", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "임플", "answer": "란트", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "루마", "answer": "니아", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "캄보", "answer": "디아", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "이탈", "answer": "리아", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "파키", "answer": "스탄", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "네덜", "answer": "란드", "difficulty": 1},
    {"problem": "이스", "answer": "라엘", "difficulty": 1}
}